<?xml version="1.0" encoding='windows-1251'?>
<doc>
	<!--
/// <include file='doc.xml' path='doc/Columns/*'/>
-->
	<Columns>
		<summary>
			Columns definitions. Set it only when the panel has no files.
		</summary>
		<remarks>
			Items of this array are similar to <c>Format-Table</c> parameter <c>-Property</c> items.
			Strings define properties and the same column names; hashtables provide more information:
			properties or script blocks, column titles, widths, types, and format strings.
			See <see cref="Meta"/> remarks about use of dictionaries as items
			and <see cref="PanelModeInfo.Columns"/> about column types.
			<para>
				Columns of <see cref="DataPanel"/> can be mapped only to properties,
				that is to data table fields. Script blocks are not supported.
			</para>
			<para>
				Special case: 'N' column (Name) of <see cref="ItemPanel"/> is always mapped to the <c>PSChildName</c>
				for providers with container items (e.g. Registry). For this column any custom data source is ignored.
				But it has to be included to describe other information: position, title, width, format string.
				Note: if column types are not specified then normally the first column is treated as 'N'.
			</para>
		</remarks>
	</Columns>
	<AddLookup>
		<summary>
			Adds a lookup handler.
		</summary>
		<param name="name">
			Name of a <see cref="ListPanel"/> file.
		</param>
		<param name="handler">Handler of [Enter] on a file.</param>
		<remarks>
			<para>
				These handles are used by <see cref="ListPanel"/> but often they are added to
				<see cref="TablePanel"/> and then internally passed in its child <see cref="ListPanel"/>.
			</para>
			<para>
				Example: if this is a <see cref="DataPanel"/> then the added handler will be called when
				[Enter] is pressed on its child <see cref="MemberPanel"/> file with the specified name.
				Normally the task of this handler is to start another table containing values to be selected
				and to set a handler triggered on [Enter] there (see <see cref="SetLookup"/>).
				Example script: <c>Test-Panel-DbNotes-.ps1</c>.
			</para>
		</remarks>
	</AddLookup>
</doc>
