<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc>
	<!--
	/// <include file='doc.xml' path='doc/IsTouched/*'/>
	/// <include file='doc.xml' path='doc/N1[@name="N2"]/*'/>
	-->
	<Experimental>
		<para>
			WARNING: This feature should work fine but it is experimental.
			It is not yet clear that it is needed. User feedback is welcome.
		</para>
	</Experimental>
	<EditorList>
		<para>
			This list is only for iterations, access by indexes, and removal by
			indexes. Accessed lines allow changes but new strings should not
			contain line separators. Other editor changes during using this
			list may cause unexpected results and should be avoided.
		</para>
	</EditorList>
	<RegisterModule>
		<para>
			If you plan to unregister this action then keep the returned reference and call its <see cref="IModuleAction.Unregister"/> later.
			Instead of keeping the reference you can get it by its ID by the <see cref="IFar"/>.<c>GetModule*()</c> methods.
		</para>
	</RegisterModule>
	<ActionGuid>
		<para>
			It is mandatory to set the action ID by <c>System.Runtime.InteropServices.GuidAttribute</c>.
			The ID has to be generated exactly for this class and it should never change.
			FarNet uses this ID internally for storing and restoring data.
			Other modules may use this ID to access and call this action.
		</para>
	</ActionGuid>
	<UseLastHistory>
		<summary>
			Tells to use the last history as the initial text if it is not set.
		</summary>
	</UseLastHistory>
	<WrapCursor>
		<summary>
			Tells to use the wrap cursor mode.
		</summary>
		<remarks>
			In the wrap cursor mode moving the cursor up from the first element or down from the last element
			moves the cursor to the bottom or the top.
		</remarks>
	</WrapCursor>
	<AutoAssignHotkeys>
		<summary>
			Tells to assigns item hotkeys automatically starting with the first item.
		</summary>
	</AutoAssignHotkeys>
	<ExpandEnvironmentVariables>
		<summary>
			Tells to expand environment variables in the input text.
		</summary>
	</ExpandEnvironmentVariables>
	<ButtonClicked>
		<summary>
			Called on the button clicks and similar actions.
		</summary>
	</ButtonClicked>
	<ShowAmpersand>
		<summary>
			Tells to show ampersand symbols in the text instead of using them as hotkey marks.
		</summary>
	</ShowAmpersand>
	<CenterGroup>
		<summary>
			Tells that the control if one of the centered group.
		</summary>
		<remarks>
			Sequential items having this flag set and the same vertical coordinates are centered horizontally.
			Their horizontal coordinates are ignored.
		</remarks>
	</CenterGroup>
	<NoFocus>
		<summary>
			Tells that the control cannot get focus. But it still processes other events.
		</summary>
	</NoFocus>
	<HelpTopic>
		<summary>
			Describes a help topic. See <see cref="IFar.ShowHelp"/> for details.
		</summary>
	</HelpTopic>
	<LT>
		<param name="left">Left position.</param>
		<param name="top">Top line.</param>
	</LT>
	<LTB>
		<param name="left">Left position.</param>
		<param name="top">Top line.</param>
		<param name="bottom">Bottom line.</param>
	</LTB>
	<LTR>
		<param name="left">Left position.</param>
		<param name="top">Top line.</param>
		<param name="right">Right position.</param>
	</LTR>
	<LTRB>
		<param name="left">Left position.</param>
		<param name="top">Top line.</param>
		<param name="right">Right position.</param>
		<param name="bottom">Bottom line.</param>
	</LTRB>
	<ShowHelp>
		<summary>Shows the specified topic from a given hlf-file.</summary>
		<param name="path">Help file location, see options.</param>
		<param name="topic">Help topic. If this parameter is empty, then the topic "Contents" is used.</param>
		<param name="options">Help options describing path and topic.</param>
		<remarks>
			The <c>topic</c> parameter describes a help topic and can be in one of the following formats:
			<code>
				<![CDATA[
"Topic"
Reference to a topic in the help file.

":Topic"
Reference to a topic from the main Far Manager help file.

"<FullPath\>Topic"
Reference to a topic in a help file located in a folder with full or relative
path of FullPath. An ending backslash must be added. The reference must not be
split on multiple lines. For example, the help file is located in the folder
"D:\Far\FarNet\Modules\Foo" and we need the topic "FooInfo" from it:
"<D:\Far\FarNet\Modules\Foo\>FooInfo"

"<FullModuleName>Topic"
Reference to a topic in a help file located in the same folder as the module
with the relative or full path of FullModuleName. The reference must not be
split on mutiple lines. For example, we need the help topic "FooInfo" from the
help file of the module Foo "D:\Far\FarNet\Modules\Foo\Foo.dll":
"<D:\Far\FarNet\Modules\Foo\Foo.dll>FooInfo"
]]>
			</code>
		</remarks>
	</ShowHelp>
	<Colors>
		<param name="foregroundColor">Foreground color.</param>
		<param name="backgroundColor">Background color.</param>
	</Colors>
	<Include>
		<summary>
			Creates and shows <see cref="IInputBox"/>.
			Note: <see cref="IInputBox.EmptyEnabled"/> is set to true.
			If you need more input box options, use the interface directly.
		</summary>
	</Include>
	<FileMask>
		<summary>
			File(s) mask, see Far API help topic [File masks]; format "include|exclude" is also supported.
			This value is only the default suggestion, actual mask may be changed by a user.
		</summary>
	</FileMask>
	<BaseListItems>
		<summary>
			List item collection. STOP: see remarks.
		</summary>
		<remarks>
			Normally you fill the list with items and set their properties before opening a
			dialog. After opening this collection is mapped to a control dynamically, i.e.
			all operations (set, insert, remove and etc.) are displayed immediately. The
			items themselves are not mapped dynamically, so that if you change an item then
			you have to reset it explicitly, see the example.
			<para>
				Dynamic mapping is simple, useful and effective when you change (or add, remove)
				one item at a time (or just a few items). But if you actually recreate all the
				items then for better performance you have to use <see cref="DetachItems"/>
				before changes and <see cref="AttachItems"/> after changes.
			</para>
		</remarks>
		<example>
			(PowerShell): how to set an item checked when the dialog is running
			<code>
				<![CDATA[
# get an item
$item = $listbox.Items[3]
# change it
$item.Checked = $true
# set it!
$listbox.Items[3] = $item
]]>
			</code>
		</example>
	</BaseListItems>
</doc>
